charismanews.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy — Charisma Magazine

At Charisma Media, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to send you information about the latest products and services and to learn from you about new products and services that you would like us to provide. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

### What information do we collect? How will we use it?

When you sign up for our newsletters, we need to know your e-mail address, first and last name. We gather this information only to get a better understanding of who you are and better serve you. We may use your name in order to personalize communications we have with you.

When you sign up for a web-based (online) or print subscription online, we collect your name, address, phone number, payment information and e-mail address. This is done so we can send the issues to you by mail or grant you access to our online subscriber's area. Us or our partners may also use the information collected to occasionally notify you about special promotions, events and products updates, services and special offers you may find valuable.

We do not sell your personal information to others. However, we do rent our customer list of subscribers from our print magazine versions and offer our email lists available to our partners of those subscribers who have "opt-in." We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related demographic information to our partners, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

Our site's registration, order and survey forms require users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the these forms are used to ship purchases and information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the you when necessary.

### Use of Cookies

"Cookies" are a form of information that can be stored on your computer by a web server for a variety of reasons. The Charisma Media Online (SCO) uses cookies, but our online visitors should be assured that cookies are simply used by us to facilitate automated activity that:

  1. Passes no significant information about the user to the Internet or to Charisma Media
  2. Is not analyzed to yield any information. We use "cookies" for the following interaction with our websites:

### Navigation and Personalization:

Some actions that a user may take in SCO, particularly during web publishing, may cause us to take the user through a series of steps that can be entered from a variety of locations. To make sure that we return the user to where they expect to be when they complete these steps, SCO will frequently send the user's browser a cookie to mark their current location. This sort of web server "bookmark" helps us to provide a positive, predictable user experience for more sophisticated operations. If you choose to personalize your online visit with us by providing your name and city, we set a permanent cookie to display the information each time you visit. This "cookie" can be disabled or removed within your browser settings. However, browsers that have cookies disabled will always remain at "guest" status. We also use them to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.

We do not use cookies for any other purpose, although this may change as we offer new features.

### Bulletin Board, Forums and Online Chat

This site has chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. SCO is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Security of Information Collected

The customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. Charisma Media maintains personal information gathered online in a secure environment protected from unauthorized third party access, alteration, or misuse. Information collected from online visitors is stored on database and other servers kept in secure locations under the custody and control of Charisma Media or its third party vendors. Charisma Media also uses technologies and processes such as encryption, access control procedures and network firewalls to protect such servers. User accounts and related information are password protected using industry-standard, commercially reasonable methods. Charisma Media makes commercially reasonable efforts to protect such information and to limit its use and disclosure of such information as described herein, but cannot guarantee that such efforts will be successful.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
  4. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
  5. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
  6. We will NOT provide any links to websites that are unsuitable for children.
  7. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. Any questions regarding the information we collect from children or our parental consent policy should be directed to:

Customer Service  
Charisma Media  
600 Rinehart Rd.  
Lake Mary, FL 32746  
(407) 333-0600  

### Your consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You will not receive these updates by snail mail or email.

_Draw closer to God. Experience the presence of the Holy Spirit every month as you read Charisma magazine. Sign up now to get Charisma for as low as[$1 per issue.](https://secure.strangmagazines.com/~strangma/charisma/2015/40years/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=article%20end%20text&utm_campaign=40th%20Anniversary)_

_Get to know the Holy Spirit and how to interact with Him on a daily basis. Learn to enter God's presence and hear His voice clearly for yourself! Go deeper in your faith with **Life in the Spirit** and change your life and destiny. [Are you ready to start your journey?](http://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=article%20end%20text&utm_campaign=LITS)_

  * [

#### Trump's Prophesied Victory Nothing Short of a Modern-Day Miracle for the Nation

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-strang-report/28065-trump-s-prophesied-victory-nothing-short-of-a-modern-day-miracle-for-the-nation "More than ever, Donald Trump now needs our support and prayers.")

Now that he has been elected, we must get behind him with our prayers and support.

  * [

#### Prophecy: After Wicked Kingdom Toppled—Jezebel Curse Broken Off America

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/prophetic-insight/28075-prophecy-after-wicked-kingdom-toppled-jezebel-curse-broken-off-america "Donald Trump holds his hands out in prayer as people at a phone bank pray for him before a campaign rally.")

On Nov. 8, the church rose up with the fervor of Jehu and threw Jezebel down.

  * [

#### How God Used Jews for Jesus to Bring a Jewish Young Man to Faith

](http://www.charismamag.com/sponsored-content/28052-how-god-used-jews-for-jesus-to-bring-a-jewish-young-man-to-faith "How God Used Jews for Jesus to Bring a Jewish Young Man to Faith")

Chicago branch leader Jeremiah Zaretsky's willingness to follow God's direction impacted one young Jew's life forever.

  * [

#### Building and Repairing Bridges in a Divisive Season

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/fire-in-my-bones/28086-building-and-repairing-bridges-in-a-divisive-season "Here are some steps you can take to become a peacemaker in these divisive times.")

If you cut people out of your life because of how they voted, you are dismembering the body of ...

  *   *   * [

#### Intercede for President-Elect Trump With These Biblical Prayer Points

](http://www.charismamag.com/life/women/28064-intercede-for-president-elect-trump-with-these-biblical-prayer-points "Now that God has heard our prayers for change, we need to do this.")

Billy Graham's daughter has some insight from Scripture as to how you can pray for ...

  * [

#### 7 Biblical Tones "Coded" for Spiritual Healing

](http://www.charismamag.com/sponsored-content/28007-7-biblical-tones-coded-for-spiritual-healing "7 Biblical Tones &#34;Coded&#34; for Spiritual Healing")

These seven pieces of beautiful music written from ancient biblical manuscripts are encoded with healing frequencies. Reports have shown miraculous results after only a few minutes of listening.

  * [

#### Trump's Win an Answer to Prayer—Now the Work Begins

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-strang-report/28028-god-answered-our-prayers-now-the-work-begins "The Donald Trump "victory party" was lively Tuesday night as I celebrated with Pastor Robert Jeffress and his wife, xxxxx.")

With Donald Trump's election as president, maybe now we can begin to understand how to hear ...

  * [

#### Are You Blocking the Flow of the Holy Spirit?

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/fire-in-my-bones/28022-are-you-blocking-the-flow-of-the-holy-spirit "Are you quenching the flow of the Holy Spirit in your life?")

If God's power isn't flowing like a river in your life, you may need a new level of ...

  *   *   * [

#### Prophecy: On Election Day, a Kingdom Will Be Toppled

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/prophetic-insight/28008-prophecy-on-election-day-a-kingdom-will-be-toppled "Like Gideon's army, we must not fear even if the outcome is not what we hoped.")

A telling dream on Election Eve and six words from the Holy Spirit this morning have encouraged my ...

  * [

#### Lance Wallnau Sees a Spiritual Dimension to This Election and Believes Trump's Breakout is Nothing Short of Miraculous

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-strang-report/27989-lance-wallnau-sees-a-spiritual-dimension-to-this-election-and-believes-trump-s-breakout-is-nothing-short-of-miraculous "Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump")

Lance believes there is witchcraft involved, along with a "spirit of Jezebel," and that God ...

  * [

#### Continue Your Journey with the Holy Spirit

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Continue Your Journey with the Holy Spirit")

Follow God on the most fulfilling journey of your life with Encounter the Holy Spirit! Break away from past hurts and press into the One who wants a personal encounter with you.

  * [

#### Dream the Unimaginable In His Presence

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Dream the Unimaginable In His Presence")

Reach your full potential and be led by His Spirit. In His Presence takes you to a deeper understanding of who God is and how he communicates with us.

  * [

#### Set Your Spirit on Fire 

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Set Your Spirit on Fire ")

Receive the power and gifts that come through the Holy Spirit Baptism. Don’t go empty-handed; accept all that He has for you! His power is available to those who ask.

  * [

#### Put on the Full Armor of God

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Put on the Full Armor of God")

Break every stronghold with the power of the Holy Spirit. Use the power of your tongue to declare and decree the Word of God. Witness heaven move on your behalf.

  * [

#### Confronting the Sins in Your Family Line

](http://www.charismamag.com/spirit/spiritual-warfare/28094-confronting-the-sins-in-your-family-line-dejesus "You can inherit many of your sin struggles from your family.")

Many of our deepest battles are inherited ones.

  * [

#### Avoiding Jezebel's Passive-Aggressive Codependency Trap

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-plumb-line/28098-avoiding-jezebel-s-passive-aggressive-codependency-trap "Symptoms of a passive-aggressive disorder include contradictory behavior.")

Ahab is passive. Jezebel is aggressive. Together, they create a deadly, codependent power couple ...

  * [

#### How God Used Jews for Jesus to Bring a Jewish Young Man to Faith

](http://www.charismamag.com/sponsored-content/28052-how-god-used-jews-for-jesus-to-bring-a-jewish-young-man-to-faith "How God Used Jews for Jesus to Bring a Jewish Young Man to Faith")

Chicago branch leader Jeremiah Zaretsky's willingness to follow God's direction impacted one young Jew's life forever.

  * [

#### How God Healed Me From Acid Reflux and Stomach Pain

](http://www.charismamag.com/life/health/28082-how-god-healed-me-from-acid-reflux-and-stomach-pain "Healing stomach pain")

As soon as God addressed these emotional issues with him, author and teacher Mark DeJesus found ...

  *   *   * [

#### 5 Truths to Understand When Leading Leaders

](http://ministrytodaymag.com/leadership/counseling/22643-5-truths-to-understand-when-leading-leaders?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=Native%20Ad%20Under%20Article "5 Truths to Understand When Leading Leaders")

If you are in leadership for any length of time, there will probably come a time where you will need to lead other leaders.

  * [

#### 7 Biblical Tones "Coded" for Spiritual Healing

](http://www.charismamag.com/sponsored-content/28007-7-biblical-tones-coded-for-spiritual-healing "7 Biblical Tones &#34;Coded&#34; for Spiritual Healing")

These seven pieces of beautiful music written from ancient biblical manuscripts are encoded with healing frequencies. Reports have shown miraculous results after only a few minutes of listening.

  * [

#### This Is Crucial to Embracing the Flow of Anointing Through Your Life

](http://www.charismamag.com/spirit/supernatural/28055-this-is-crucial-to-embracing-the-flow-of-anointing-through-your-life "Anointing ")

It will help you go higher and higher and see your anointing increase.

  * [

#### Waiting or Warring: Contending for Prophetic Purposes

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/a-voice-calling-out/28051-waiting-or-warring-contending-for-prophetic-purposes "God has called you to fight!")

When God has given a prophetic promise, how are we to respond?

  * [

#### How You Can Be Part of God's Rising Remnant

](http://www.charismamag.com/spirit/revival/28031-how-you-can-be-part-of-god-s-rising-remnant "Will you stand up and be part of God's rising remnant?")

Now is not the time to hide in a cave and be indifferent.

  * [

#### The Kingdom Attitude That Kills the Urge to Quit Your Diet

](http://www.charismamag.com/life/health/28044-the-kingdom-attitude-that-kills-the-urge-to-quit-your-diet "Gluttony attitude")

This can save you a lot of time and frustration.

  *   *   * [

#### Jesus' Millennial Reign: Believers Have Reason to Shout

](http://www.charismamag.com/spirit/prophecy/28049-jesus-millennial-reign-believers-have-reason-to-shout "Believers have a great reason to be excited about Jesus' Millennial reign.")

Here's why it will be a joyous time.

  * [

#### Your Healing Role After a Divisive Election Season

](http://www.charismamag.com/life/women/28048-your-healing-role-after-a-divisive-election-season "With such a close election, your candidate either became president or didn't get elected. Either way, this very close election split the nation. This is what we can do moving forward to build a bridge.")

This election cycle has been difficult and hurtful for all sides. Discover what you can do to help ...

  * [

#### Standing Strong in the Sudden Storms of Life

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-plumb-line/28017-standing-strong-in-the-sudden-storms-of-life "The storms of life can blindside you. Stay strong in Jesus.")

I was already fighting four or five other spiritual battles, and this was a major blindside.

  * [

#### God's Power at Work in the Church Today

](http://www.charismamag.com/blogs/the-strang-report?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "God&#39;s Power at Work in the Church Today")

Charisma's founder, Steve Strang writes about today's hottest topics affecting the Christian faith.

  * [

#### 4 Ways to Love Your Wife Even When You Don't Like Her

](http://www.charismamag.com/life/men/27979-4-ways-to-love-your-wife-even-when-you-don-t-like-her "You can still love your wife, even if you don't like her at times.")

When she frustrates you, practice these things, and it will enhance your relationship.

  * [

#### Continue Your Journey with the Holy Spirit

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Continue Your Journey with the Holy Spirit")

Follow God on the most fulfilling journey of your life with Encounter the Holy Spirit! Break away from past hurts and press into the One who wants a personal encounter with you.

  * [

#### Dream the Unimaginable In His Presence

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Dream the Unimaginable In His Presence")

Reach your full potential and be led by His Spirit. In His Presence takes you to a deeper understanding of who God is and how he communicates with us.

  * [

#### Set Your Spirit on Fire 

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Set Your Spirit on Fire ")

Receive the power and gifts that come through the Holy Spirit Baptism. Don’t go empty-handed; accept all that He has for you! His power is available to those who ask.

  * [

#### Put on the Full Armor of God

](https://lifeinthespiritbooks.com/?utm_source=charismamag.com&utm_medium=native%20ad "Put on the Full Armor of God")

Break every stronghold with the power of the Holy Spirit. Use the power of your tongue to declare and decree the Word of God. Witness heaven move on your behalf.
